<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addons>
<addon id="plugin.video.adulthideout" name="AdultHideout" version="1.0.9" provider-name="Vashiel">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.25.1"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <settingfile>resources/settings.xml</settingfile>
        <news>
v. 1.0.9 "Cloud Nine" - 2026-04-20
- **10 New Sites**: ArchiveBate, CamCaps, Chaturbate, HentaiDude, HentaiOcean, Ikisoda, JAVHDPorn, Perverzija, PMVHaven (by user request), XOpenload.
- **Improved and Fixed**: AVJoy, WatchPorn.
- **ArchiveBate**: Right-click filters (Gender, Sort), local thumbnail proxy-cache for CDN bypass, Livewire routing fixes.
- **AVJoy**: Page/session/stream caching, curl.exe/curl_cffi fetch paths, pre-resolving for visible videos, seek-aware local curl proxy for slow CDN streams.
- **CamCaps and Chaturbate**: Search, categories, Sort By, pagination, and hardened playback (Lulu HLS proxy, Clicknplay fast-start, Chaturbate room proxy).
- **Hentai/JAV**: HentaiDude (subtitles, pagination, dashboard fallback), HentaiOcean (API/RSS, direct MP4), Ikisoda (KVS direct MP4), JAVHDPorn (Cloudflare-aware, StreamTape/HugStream resolver).
- **PMVHaven and Perverzija**: API pagination, search, categories, Sort By; Perverzija adds Cloudflare-hardened listings and XtremeStream HLS.
- **XOpenload**: Full-length movie support with multi-hoster resolver (MixDrop, StreamTape, DoodStream, Voe).
- **WatchPorn**: Removed fragile local proxy path, fixed seek stability via direct header-based playback.
- **Removed**: MaturePorn.Tube (404 only).
- **Core Engine**: Updated vendored cloudscraper stack, added small resolver ports, kept networking pure-Python for Android/Fire TV.
- **10th Anniversary Year**: 1.0.9 continues the next expansion wave of AdultHideout's anniversary year.
        </news>
        <summary>[COLOR red]XXX[/COLOR] Porn videos</summary>
        <description>
Internet [COLOR red]XXX Porn Video[COLOR white] Streams.

[COLOR red][B]WARNING:[/B][COLOR red]Only for adults[/COLOR]

[COLOR white]AdultHideout does not host third-party videos on its own servers and is not affiliated with the websites supported by the addon.
Content, streams and metadata are provided by third-party websites.[/COLOR]

[COLOR white]Github:
https://github.com/Vashiel/repository.adulthideout
[/COLOR]
        </description>
        <disclaimer>AdultHideout does not host third-party videos on its own servers and is not affiliated with the websites supported by the addon. Content, streams and metadata are provided by third-party websites.</disclaimer>
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>http://www.gnu.org/licenses/</license>
        <forum></forum>
        <website></website>
        <email></email>
        <mainsource>https://github.com/Vashiel/repository.adulthideout</mainsource>
        <source></source>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/logos/icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>resources/logos/fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>
</addons>
