<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="plugin.video.adulthideout" name="AdultHideout" version="1.0.14" provider-name="Vashiel">
    <requires>
        <import addon="xbmc.python" version="3.0.0"/>
        <import addon="script.module.requests" version="2.25.1"/>
    </requires>
    <extension point="xbmc.python.pluginsource" library="default.py">
        <provides>video</provides>
    </extension>
    <extension point="xbmc.service" library="resources/lib/view_service.py" start="startup"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <settingfile>resources/settings.xml</settingfile>
        <news>
v. 1.0.14 "Featherlight" - 2026-06-14
- **Global Search 2.0**: Reworked global search with selectable sources, Select All Sites, combined presets, cached result pages, stable return-to-results after playback and playable-video-only results.
- **Featherlight Optimization**: Major addon size and cleanup pass; compressed logo assets and removed stale caches, unused vendor modules and verification leftovers while preserving Android/Cloudflare compatibility.
- **Vendor Cleanup**: Trimmed unused cloudscraper captcha integrations, optional JS interpreters, requests_toolbelt, charset_normalizer, six, obsolete browser metadata and unused IDNA UTS-46 data, then verified the remaining networking stack.
- **Settings Cleanup**: Cleaned site toggles, duplicate settings and mouse-navigation hitbox issues so active sites and sort options stay aligned.
- **New Site**: Added JizzBerry with newest/top listings, search, filtered categories, pagination, real site icon and highest-quality direct MP4 playback/recording support.
- **New Site**: Added MyLust with listings, search, filtered video categories, pagination, sorting, real homepage logo and highest-quality direct MP4 playback/recording support.
- **New Site**: Added Hentaisea with latest episodes, series listings, search, filtered genre categories, pagination, real homepage logo and DooPlay/JWPlayer signed MP4 playback/recording support.
- **New Site**: Added PimpBunny with listings, search, categories, model directory, pagination, sorting, real homepage logo and high-quality KVS MP4 playback/recording support.
- **New Site**: Added ShesFreaky with listings, search, categories, pagination, sorting, real homepage logo and direct MP4 playback/recording support.

v. 1.0.13 "Rangefinder" - 2026-06-13
- **New Site**: Added MyPornTape with listings, search, categories, models, pagination, sorting, real homepage logo and KVS MP4 playback/recording support.
- **New Site**: Added FamilyPornHD with listings, categories, search, pagination, real homepage logo and WatchStreamHD HLS resolver playback.
- **New Resolver**: Added WatchStreamHD resolver that rewrites CDN-auth HLS playlists to fully qualified URLs for seek-safe local playback.
- **New Site**: Added PornoBae with listings, search, categories, pagination and playback via the custom TubexPlayer HLS resolver.
- **Experimental Site**: Added AllPornStream as a contained catalog/mirror experiment with listings, search, actors, categories, producers, pagination and playback via the shared resolver preference stack.
- **AllPornStream/MyDaddy**: Added a shared MyDaddy resolver that follows the browser alt-player path and resolves old MyDaddy-only posts to fresh BigCDN MP4 streams.
- **New Site**: Added Xtapes with listings, search, categories, pagination, sort options, real homepage logo and shared 88z HLS resolver playback/recording support.
- **New Resolver**: Added reusable 88z player resolution with encrypted API decoding and HLS stream probing for sites using the same embed player.
- **New Site**: Added CamgirlFap with listings, search, categories, models, pagination, sorting, cached thumbnails, real homepage logo and KVS MP4 playback/recording support through the seek-safe local Range proxy.
- **Sextb.net**: Added shared resolver preferences, resolver enable switches and pre-playback stream health checks so unstable/dead server choices can fall through to the next supported resolver before playback starts.
- **Global Search**: Filtered captured results to playable video items only, preventing source Search/Categories/Models navigation entries from appearing in global result pages.
- **Playback Proxy**: Fixed urllib proxy seek handling by giving each Range request its own cancel signal, preventing stale connections from surviving fast seeks.
- **CamgirlFap Playback**: Fixed stream probe rejecting plain MP4 URLs without quality suffix; both quality-tagged and plain links are now probed and accepted.
- **Playback Proxy DNS**: Fixed intermittent seek freezes (Windows Errno 11002) with pre-resolve IP cache and http.client fallback so seeks never need a fresh DNS lookup.

v. 1.0.12 "Signal Lock" - 2026-06-01
- **85po Android**: Fixed Android/Kodi Cloudflare 403 failures by reusing a browser-like session for listings, parsing and MP4 delivery.
- **LuxureTV**: Repaired listing extraction after the site markup changed and made metadata parsing resilient when durations are missing.
- **FFmpeg Recorder**: Added the "Video herunterladen" context action, shared stream resolution hooks and in-process proxy routing for protected downloads.
- **Recording Support**: Enabled FFmpeg recording paths for 85po, HStream, Ikisoda and XXXTube.
- **New Site**: Added AllowFlash with listings, search, categories, pagination, premium filtering, DNS retry handling and seek-safe MP4 playback through a local Range proxy.
- **New Site**: Added NotFans with listings, search, tag categories, pagination, sorting and KVS MP4 playback.
- **New Site**: Added WOW.xxx with listings, search, categories, pagination, sorting and configurable MP4 quality preference.
- **New Site**: Added XXThots with listings, search, categories, pagination, sorting and Android-safe proxy-backed MP4 playback.
- **New Site**: Added JAVSubbed.net with listings, categories (English Subbed, Censored, Uncensored), actress directory, studios, search, and dynamic resolver playback and recording support.
- **New Site**: Added Sextb.net with listings, categories (Amateur, Censored, Uncensored, English Subtitle), search, actress/studio/genre directories, pagination, and player decryption support.
- **New Site**: Added Porn4Fans with listings, search, categories, models, pagination, sorting, cached thumbnails and KVS MP4 playback/recording support.
- **New Site**: Added YesPornVIP with listings, search, models, pagination, sorting and KVS MP4 playback/recording support.
- **New Site**: Added Tgtsporn with listings, search, models, pagination, sorting and KVS MP4 playback/recording support.
- **New Site**: Added PornMedium with listings, search, categories, pagination, sorting and MP4 quality selection.
- **KVS Engine**: Added reusable KVSTubeWebsite base class for rapid KVS tube site integration.
- **Global Search**: Added a controlled multi-site search entry with selectable sources, source presets, progressive paging, profile-aware result caching, stable return-to-results behavior after playback and per-source result limits to avoid slow all-site scans.
- **NoodleMagazine**: Reworked playback resolution to use the official nmcorp player playlist before falling back to raw page MP4 extraction, avoiding stale CDN77 403 links.
- **View Settings**: Restored persistent view selection while avoiding per-page overrides of Kodi-side view changes.
- **Removed**: UFlash, because the site now requires login/paywall access for playable streams and no longer provides public video URLs.
- **Stability**: Hardened recording directory creation and directory action termination across Windows and Android Kodi setups.
        </news>
        <summary>[COLOR red]XXX[/COLOR] Porn videos</summary>
        <description>
Internet [COLOR red]XXX Porn Video[COLOR white] Streams.

[COLOR red][B]WARNING:[/B][COLOR red]Only for adults[/COLOR]    

[COLOR white]AdultHideout does not host third-party videos on its own servers and is not affiliated with the websites supported by the addon.
Content, streams and metadata are provided by third-party websites.[/COLOR]

[COLOR white]Github:
https://github.com/Vashiel/repository.adulthideout
[/COLOR]    
        </description>
        <disclaimer>AdultHideout does not host third-party videos on its own servers and is not affiliated with the websites supported by the addon. Content, streams and metadata are provided by third-party websites.</disclaimer>    
        <platform>all</platform>
        <license>http://www.gnu.org/licenses/</license>
        <forum></forum>
        <website></website>    
        <email></email>
        <mainsource>https://github.com/Vashiel/repository.adulthideout</mainsource>    
        <source></source>         
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/logos/icon.png</icon>
            <fanart>resources/logos/fanart.jpg</fanart>
        </assets>
    </extension>
</addon>

